There it is!
"Hotel Mythos"
Ow, ow!
Ah, I'm fine. Please don't be frightened.
Thank you.
You're the one who found this coin, aren't you?
"Academic Advisor"
"The AC is broken"
You're sure you're okay with that, Kagaya?
Huh?
Don't you think turning it
down is a bit of a waste?
Your grades are certainly good enough for...
I think you might be giving me too much credit.
Sorry about that, Kagaya. Well, hmm.
It'd be a long trip every day, from this town--
You'd have to find a dorm or something
near the college, and you'd be living alone.
But don't worry about that.
We can help you work it out.
Thank you.
But I'd like to think things over a bit more.
Oh, okay.
"Gaio University" "Kuroyama Gakuin University"
"Nanyou University" "Nimoku University"
"Oseda University"
Kagaya, did you find
something you want to pursue?
Yeah, I guess.
That's a lie.
But that's normal, right?
Well, Kaga? Did you get a recommendation?
I guess I shouldn't set my sights so high.
Oh. Well, don't worry about it.
Professor Kagaya!
Can you show me your work?
Sure. There you go.
Thank you!
Ooh!
--What is it, Nana?
--You know his recommendation
was just denied, right?
--Hmm? Oh, nothing.
--You know his recommendation
was just denied, right?
--Who wants to go to college anyway?
--Normal is best.
--Being the same as everyone
else makes me feel calm.
--Let's get temp jobs! That's where the fun is!
--I don't need to "be myself."
--You can polish lenses in factories!
Ugh, I'm way too tired for gym class.
We're running a marathon today.
Seriously? It's hot as hell, are they crazy?
What's up?
Nothing.
Just pretend not to see it.
No need to stick your neck out.
After all, I'm...
The number you are trying
to reach is no longer in service.
Please confirm the number and dial again.
Okay, be back in a bit!
Okay!
Good luck, Nana!
I wonder if it got hit by a car
or something. Stupid tanuki.
Hey, Izumi!
Your underwear...
Ugh!
Kaga, you're looking right at it!
Try to be more subtle, man!
Huh?!
Kagaya, you creep!
Her wrist snap on that throw was so sharp...
Hi there!
Mifune!
Hey, did you hear?
I got a college recommendation!
Oh, congrats--
To be honest, I didn't think
my chances were great.
Look what my mom said when I told her!
"Congratulations!"
Really? That's great.
Sorry, I'm going to get back to cleaning.
It was supposed to be you, wasn't it?
The one to get the recommendation.
Why?
It was your skill that got the recommendation.
Thank you.
Oh!
You've got mud on your pants.
What happened?
Oh, nothing.
The truth is, I no longer have
any problems with my vision.
My eyes just seemed
to get better out of nowhere.
That's right. My body,
for some reason... At some point...
A fire?
And it's close!
I've got to call 119!
That smell...
Is someone... inside?
No. Don't stick your neck out.
But... There's a beast inside me!
I don't know how I got this power.
Why do I have this sense of smell?
And...
This strange, monstrous form!
I just don't understand!
And of all the things I could
transform into, why a stuffed animal?
Why a dog?
It's all so crazy...
Enough. Stay focused, save this person.
It's hard to move,
and my field of vision is bad.
No time to mess around.
Got to hurry.
What the hell have I become?
Whatever it is, it allowed me to rescue her.
"The beast has saved the day!"
Or something like that.
More like, "the cute mascot has saved the day!"
Well, it was useful this time.
I guess that's okay.
And nobody saw me.
What is this? Her smell...
What am I doing?!
Our next story--
This morning, before dawn,
a possible arsonist fire broke out
at a small industrial garage
in the logging district.
"Fire at logging building
in the mountains-- Arson?"
at a small industrial garage
in the logging district.
"Fire at logging building
in the mountains-- Arson?"
There do not appear to be
any related deaths or injuries.
"Fire at logging building
in the mountains-- Arson?"
According to the fire department,
--Oh wow, that's pretty close. How scary.
--evidence at the scene indicated
kerosene had been spread around,
--Oh wow, that's pretty close. How scary.
--and authorities have begun
investigating a potential arson.
Why is my phone gone?!
No way. Did I leave it there?
What should I do?
--If the cops investigate me,
and my secret gets out...
--Hey!
--If the cops investigate me,
and my secret gets out...
--Oh, hi!
--If the cops investigate me,
and my secret gets out...
That smell...
Shuichi Kagaya.
This is your phone, isn't it?
I knew you were out there.
Nobody believed me. I thought I might be crazy.
I can't believe you were hiding right here.
Mind if I ask you some questions?
I can't help but be curious...
...about a monster like you.
Her smell...
No, stay focused!
I've got to get my phone back!
It's not here.
There you are, monster.
I was hoping that if everyone
found out who you really are,
you might go on a rampage here at school.
I'm a little disappointed.
Thank you for picking up my phone.
Huh. You sound so sincere.
But what exactly do you mean by "monster"?
Even if she saw me in my transformed state,
there's no proof that that was me.
And think about the state she was in.
She probably wasn't fully conscious.
Maybe if I pretend she was hallucinating...
Like I asked this morning,
did you see something?
Oh! I guess I've made a mistake.
Here's your phone.
Still, it's strange.
I could have sworn I saw it.
A monster that almost violated me.
Smile for the camera!
That's a good one.
Hmm. You're more handsome in this form.
You don't mind standing out here in plain sight?
What happened, Nana?
Did I just imagine that?
Is this a real gun?
I don't know! I think it's a toy.
That's enough! If someone sees me...
Sorry. Not until you tell me about this form.
If you don't, I'll tell
everyone that you're a monster.
Wouldn't that be fun?
How will people react if
they find out monsters are real?
You might be famous, get to be on TV.
Or you might get sliced up like a lab rat.
Probably that one.
You'll be left alive,
swarmed over like some kind of toy.
I don't know anything! Really. Nothing!
It just started out of nowhere.
The transforming.
I have no idea what it is!
Fine then. But if you're lying,
I'll be very upset.
Why did this happen?
Oh, I just realized I haven't introduced myself.
My name is Clair Aoki.
What a trashy-- I mean, what a fancy name.
I'm a first year.
She's younger than me? And by two years!
What's with that face?
Oh, nothing!
By the way, Shuichi...
Isn't it a little soon to use my first name?!
Do you know what this is?
No, I've never seen it. Is it a coin?
It seems to be related
to you monsters somehow...
"You monsters"?
If you don't know, that's fine.
Hang on a sec!
Don't just stand there. Let's go.
Come on in. This is my place.
Make yourself at home.
I'm the only one who lives here.
Ah, it was so hot out there. I hate summer.
All the bugs... And if you're
not careful, you get sunburned.
This is my first time in a girl's room.
Or, I mean, home!
Hold on, what are you doing?
Changing, obviously.
Changing...?
All that stress made me sweat.
Is she one of those nudists?!
No, she still has her underwear on...
Nevermind!
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Completely unavoidable in a situation like this.
A perfectly natural biological
reaction for a mature male.
Be a good boy and wait there.
If you move, I'll kill you.
Don't forget, you've got to do as I say now.
I saved you, remember?
If it wasn't for me, you'd have died!
I'm your--
That's right.
You completely ruined my suicide.
Like I said, nobody believed me
when I told them monsters are real.
But I finally found one.
Clair, what are you...?
You'll help me, won't you, Shuichi?
Do you know them?
Nope.
Shuichi, they're an enemy!
Enemy?
Who the hell are you? Barging in like that--
Give me the coin.
Coin... You mean this?
I see. You want it, so you must know what it is.
Psh.
Maybe you'd like to share.
What the hell is this thing?
The coin...
In exchange for power, you lose everything.
Give me the coin.
Don't kill her now, Shuichi.
I've got some questions for her.
Of course I'm not going to kill her!
Why would I do that?!
Hold still!
Let's take a step back here.
Why don't you introduce yourself?
Come on, out with it. What's your name?
Oh, I get it. You guys are gatherers, too.
I guess I don't need this, then.
I don't care who comes for me...
Or how many of you there are...
I'll rip you apart!
You're... like me...
A monster.
Pathetic!
"Episode 2: What It Means to Be Empty"